[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", ",", "``", "NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Where does it move from that to the severity of what has happened here, in other words where there's a genuine risk that somebody may take their life?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "it", "move", "from", "that", "to", "the", "severity", "of", "what", "has", "happened", "here", ",", "in", "other", "words", "where", "there", "'s", "a", "genuine", "risk", "that", "somebody", "may", "take", "their", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, they were saying stuff like, \"Go kill yourself.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "were", "saying", "stuff", "like", ",", "``", "Go", "kill", "yourself", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Where does it lie at the moment and where do you think it should be?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "it", "lie", "at", "the", "moment", "and", "where", "do", "you", "think", "it", "should", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Unfortunately, there's not a lot of responsibility put on parent's shoulders to the way their kids act online.", "answer_tokens": ["Unfortunately", ",", "there", "'s", "not", "a", "lot", "of", "responsibility", "put", "on", "parent", "'s", "shoulders", "to", "the", "way", "their", "kids", "act", "online", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "How do you regulate what you can't get access to?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "regulate", "what", "you", "ca", "n't", "get", "access", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, Piers, you can get access to it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "can", "get", "access", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "At the same time, having had, you know, three teenage kids, how far can you really say parents have to be legally responsible to every word they may post on social media?", "question_tokens": ["At", "the", "same", "time", ",", "having", "had", ",", "you", "know", ",", "three", "teenage", "kids", ",", "how", "far", "can", "you", "really", "say", "parents", "have", "to", "be", "legally", "responsible", "to", "every", "word", "they", "may", "post", "on", "social", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "I don't think they can be for every word.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "they", "can", "be", "for", "every", "word", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "How far do you take it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "far", "do", "you", "take", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Piers, I absolutely do.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "absolutely", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What should the law do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "the", "law", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, Piers, there's one thing that's very much missing from this conversation and that is a whole lot more support for the victim of the bullying or the stalking or both.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "there", "'s", "one", "thing", "that", "'s", "very", "much", "missing", "from", "this", "conversation", "and", "that", "is", "a", "whole", "lot", "more", "support", "for", "the", "victim", "of", "the", "bullying", "or", "the", "stalking", "or", "both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "What is the best sensible way to frame a law that can deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "best", "sensible", "way", "to", "frame", "a", "law", "that", "can", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Well, it's very hard because you have to balance on the one hand freedom of speech and freedom of expression against the very understandable needs of the victim.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "hard", "because", "you", "have", "to", "balance", "on", "the", "one", "hand", "freedom", "of", "speech", "and", "freedom", "of", "expression", "against", "the", "very", "understandable", "needs", "of", "the", "victim", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What is your thinking on all this from your crisis point of view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "thinking", "on", "all", "this", "from", "your", "crisis", "point", "of", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, first of all I have a 15 year old and an eight year old.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", "I", "have", "a", "15", "year", "old", "and", "an", "eight", "year", "old", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Is that your man from Harvard?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "man", "from", "Harvard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, and that's exactly what I said on your show the other night.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "I", "said", "on", "your", "show", "the", "other", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harvard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Can I pay (ph) for that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "pay", "(", "ph", ")", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I'm going to make that happen if it kills me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "make", "that", "happen", "if", "it", "kills", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "What do you make of him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "First of all, beware of people who are dismissing him and beware of people who impugn his motives and I grant him sincerity and I'm a great believer in assuming somebody is sincere and just sincerely disagreeing with his views.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "beware", "of", "people", "who", "are", "dismissing", "him", "and", "beware", "of", "people", "who", "impugn", "his", "motives", "and", "I", "grant", "him", "sincerity", "and", "I", "'m", "a", "great", "believer", "in", "assuming", "somebody", "is", "sincere", "and", "just", "sincerely", "disagreeing", "with", "his", "views", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP", "Tea Party"], "LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Are you impressed by what you see in here just in terms of the way he conducts (ph) himself?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "impressed", "by", "what", "you", "see", "in", "here", "just", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "way", "he", "conducts", "(", "ph", ")", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NN", ":", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "Well, I think he's very bright but unless the GOP is on some kind of suicide mission where they would like to just go off in flames in the next election, I would say that they're not going to nominate him for president that he does obviously represent a lot of people in the Tea Party and some people in Texas who are also very conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "very", "bright", "but", "unless", "the", "GOP", "is", "on", "some", "kind", "of", "suicide", "mission", "where", "they", "would", "like", "to", "just", "go", "off", "in", "flames", "in", "the", "next", "election", ",", "I", "would", "say", "that", "they", "'re", "not", "going", "to", "nominate", "him", "for", "president", "that", "he", "does", "obviously", "represent", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "in", "the", "Tea", "Party", "and", "some", "people", "in", "Texas", "who", "are", "also", "very", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Should she still be in her job given the pretty upholding breakdown of the ObamaCare system, if she's on her watch?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "she", "still", "be", "in", "her", "job", "given", "the", "pretty", "upholding", "breakdown", "of", "the", "ObamaCare", "system", ",", "if", "she", "'s", "on", "her", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I think we need to correct the system and make it easier for people to have access, but no.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "need", "to", "correct", "the", "system", "and", "make", "it", "easier", "for", "people", "to", "have", "access", ",", "but", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Even Hillary Clinton?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "Hillary", "Clinton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Only people fainting at her and her rallies are going to be chubby gals from now.", "answer_tokens": ["Only", "people", "fainting", "at", "her", "and", "her", "rallies", "are", "going", "to", "be", "chubby", "gals", "from", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Do you think she will be the democrat nominee?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "will", "be", "the", "democrat", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I kind of hope so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "kind", "of", "hope", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Who do you most fear on the Democrats side?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "most", "fear", "on", "the", "Democrats", "side", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Who's the most electable right now?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "'s", "the", "most", "electable", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "Well, that remains to be seen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "remains", "to", "be", "seen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Could he win the election?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "he", "win", "the", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "If he were the republican candidate, OK.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "he", "were", "the", "republican", "candidate", ",", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "... who do you think can exercise your desire to have a winner?", "question_tokens": ["...", "who", "do", "you", "think", "can", "exercise", "your", "desire", "to", "have", "a", "winner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I'm not sure I want to see them in debate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "I", "want", "to", "see", "them", "in", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "Ted Cruz?", "question_tokens": ["Ted", "Cruz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Isn't he the new king of the Tea Party where she was once queen?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "he", "the", "new", "king", "of", "the", "Tea", "Party", "where", "she", "was", "once", "queen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "I don't see the analogy but I love them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "the", "analogy", "but", "I", "love", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Yes, but my point is I mean, do you think that he could be more electable to a wider cross section just to win the nomination and mind anything else and republicans?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "my", "point", "is", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "he", "could", "be", "more", "electable", "to", "a", "wider", "cross", "section", "just", "to", "win", "the", "nomination", "and", "mind", "anything", "else", "and", "republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "Well, see it's very possible.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "see", "it", "'s", "very", "possible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "And republicans don't to do that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "republicans", "do", "n't", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "No, look at how we've been doing in elections.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "look", "at", "how", "we", "'ve", "been", "doing", "in", "elections", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "How did you hear about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I didn't see it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "see", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Do you see at home (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "see", "at", "home", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I did and I started to cry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "and", "I", "started", "to", "cry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Do you believe that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "No, no, I can't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "I'm gay.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "gay", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 452, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Are you ...", "answer_tokens": ["Are", "you", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "ORGAN: When you said those words, when you're a straight man, so you're playing a gay character did you have any conception of the enormity of that moment both to the debate we just discussed but also to you and to your career?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "When", "you", "said", "those", "words", ",", "when", "you", "'re", "a", "straight", "man", ",", "so", "you", "'re", "playing", "a", "gay", "character", "did", "you", "have", "any", "conception", "of", "the", "enormity", "of", "that", "moment", "both", "to", "the", "debate", "we", "just", "discussed", "but", "also", "to", "you", "and", "to", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "The time we did that episode we were three seasons in or maybe possible, I think was three.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "time", "we", "did", "that", "episode", "we", "were", "three", "seasons", "in", "or", "maybe", "possible", ",", "I", "think", "was", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Again, going back to the Biden clip there when you look at Washington and the ridiculous shutdown of the government and squabbling of the debt ceiling, all this stuff we've all have to endure (inaudible) for the last two weeks, do you think that should be some kind of show on television which does for the Washington dysfunction what Will & Grace did for the gay marriage debate and the gay rights debate?", "question_tokens": ["Again", ",", "going", "back", "to", "the", "Biden", "clip", "there", "when", "you", "look", "at", "Washington", "and", "the", "ridiculous", "shutdown", "of", "the", "government", "and", "squabbling", "of", "the", "debt", "ceiling", ",", "all", "this", "stuff", "we", "'ve", "all", "have", "to", "endure", "(", "inaudible", ")", "for", "the", "last", "two", "weeks", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "should", "be", "some", "kind", "of", "show", "on", "television", "which", "does", "for", "the", "Washington", "dysfunction", "what", "Will", "&", "Grace", "did", "for", "the", "gay", "marriage", "debate", "and", "the", "gay", "rights", "debate", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I mean absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Will & Grace"], "LOCATION": ["Washington", "Washington"], "PERSON": ["Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "A floor and half, it's properly clenched (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["A", "floor", "and", "half", ",", "it", "'s", "properly", "clenched", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "We've grabbed each other.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ve", "grabbed", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "He's nine years old?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "nine", "years", "old", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Nine.", "answer_tokens": ["Nine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "And how many people are in the elevator?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "many", "people", "are", "in", "the", "elevator", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "There were nine of us, eight of us something like that.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "were", "nine", "of", "us", ",", "eight", "of", "us", "something", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "(Inaudible) limit?", "question_tokens": ["(", "Inaudible", ")", "limit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It could have.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "could", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "What you do up to for the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "you", "do", "up", "to", "for", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "I'm about to start rehearsal on my first Broadway play.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "about", "to", "start", "rehearsal", "on", "my", "first", "Broadway", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "But, does it have a name?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "does", "it", "have", "a", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "It does.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["TNT"]}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Eric, what are you up to?", "question_tokens": ["Eric", ",", "what", "are", "you", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "I was starting back on the third season of Perception on TNT.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "starting", "back", "on", "the", "third", "season", "of", "Perception", "on", "TNT", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131018pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "(Inaudible) with great funness with -- did you miss it?", "question_tokens": ["(", "Inaudible", ")", "with", "great", "funness", "with", "--", "did", "you", "miss", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "I totally -- the process was unlike -- the sitcom is unlike anything else.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "totally", "--", "the", "process", "was", "unlike", "--", "the", "sitcom", "is", "unlike", "anything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]